Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ minhhuunguyen (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

MLOps

Python (Programming Language)
Machine Learning

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Honors-Awards

First Prize at Student Scientific Research Contest

Nguyen Huu Minh

Al Engineer • MLOps Engineer @ PIXTA Vietnam Co. Ltd Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced researcher in some computer vision problems such as: GANs, Face Recognition, Face Attributes Classification, Tiny Object Detection, Video Classification. Engineering products by using Python with libraries such as: PyTorch, Numpy, Pandas, etc, and some other tools like Git, AWS, Docker, etc. Some soft skills while working in profession such as: presentation, leadership and teamwork.

Experience

PIXTA Vietnam Co. Ltd.

5 years 11 months

Al Engineer

February 2020 - Present (5 years 2 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

- 1. Machine learning operations (MLOps)
- 2. Face recognition: From noisy labeled datasets, building a backbone that can be used to solve both identification problem and verification problem.
- 3. Face attributes classification: Classifying face images into multi-label and multi-class attributes.
- 4. Object detection: Detecting tiny object in a high-resolution images and balancing trade-off between accuracy and performance.
- 5. Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs): Solving high-resolution images synthesis problem by using StyleGAN and controlling attributes of image generated by GANs.
- 6. Video and text classification: Combining visual features from video and embedding features from text to classify.

Al Researcher

May 2019 - January 2020 (9 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

- 1. Generative adversarial networks (GANs): Solving high-resolution images-to-image translation problem.
- 2. Noisy image classification: Classifying images which contain noisy pixels.

ProtonX

Lecturer

November 2023 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

MCI Vietnam Consultant Joint Stock Company

Lecturer

November 2021 - Present (3 years 5 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

- 1. Python for Data Science
- 2. Machine Learning
- 3. Deep Learning

Khoang Troi Cua Be

Founder & Chairman

September 2016 - Present (8 years 7 months)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

- 1. Organizing projects and events to support children following The Rights of Infants.
- 2. Training and improving soft skills for volunteers.

Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Master of Science - MS, Mathematrics and Informatics · (October 2020 - August 2022)

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Engineer's degree, Mathematics and Informatics · (August 2015 - June 2020)

High School for Gifted Students, Hanoi University of Science,

Vietnam National University

High School Diploma · (August 2012 - June 2015)